Guide to the People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (PETA) Research Files
People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (PETA) Research Files
- Experimentation, 7 linear feet
  - Falsification/Bribery—Drug Companies—American Cyanimid Co. (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Drug Companies—American Therapeutics, Inc. (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Drug Companies—BARR (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Drug Companies—Bolar (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Drug Companies—IBT (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Drug Companies—Miscellaneous (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Drug Companies—Par (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Drug Companies—Phar-Mor, Inc. (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Drug Companies—Pharma Kinetics Laboratories, Inc. (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Drug Companies—Vitarine (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Investigators (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Baltimore People (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Borer (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Breuning (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Bridges (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Cort (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Darsee (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Fisher, Bernard (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Frazier (Box 96, Folder 19)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Gallo, Robert (Box 96, Folder 20)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Hamosh, Margit (Box 96, Folder 21)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Hansen (Box 96, Folder 22)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Healy, Bernadine (Box 96, Folder 23)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Imanishi-Kari, Thereza (Box 96, Folder 24)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Long (Box 96, Folder 25)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Milanese (Box 96, Folder 26)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Miscellaneous (Box 96, Folder 27)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Needleman, Herbert (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Ninnemann, John (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Perlmutter, Marion (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Rosen, Gerald (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Salahuddin, Syed Zaki (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Sarin, Prem (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Seife, Marvin (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Slutsky (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Straus (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Summerlin (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Summers (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Falsification/Bribery—Specific People—Terry, Leon Cass. (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous—fraud—miscellaneous—in the use of government funded research - 1 of 3 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous—fraud—miscellaneous—in the use of government funded research - 2 of 3 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous—fraud—miscellaneous—in the use of government funded research - 3 of 3 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - Types of Alternatives—General - 1 of 13 (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - Types of Alternatives—General - 2 of 13 (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - Types of Alternatives—General - 3 of 13 (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Types of Alternatives—General - 4 of 13 (Box 97, Folder 19)
  - Types of Alternatives—General - 5 of 13 (Box 97, Folder 20)
  - Types of Alternatives—General - 6 of 13 (Box 97, Folder 21)
  - Types of Alternatives—General - 7 of 13 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Types of Alternatives—General - 8 of 13 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Types of Alternatives—General - 9 of 13 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Types of Alternatives—General - 10 of 13 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Types of Alternatives—General - 11 of 13 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Types of Alternatives—General - 12 of 13 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Types of Alternatives—General - 13 of 13 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Types of Alternatives—Genetic Test Systems (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Types of Alternatives—GRAS (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Types of Alternatives—Human Tests - 1 of 10 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Types of Alternatives—Human Tests - 2 of 10 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Types of Alternatives—Human Tests - 3 of 10 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Types of Alternatives—Human Tests - 4 of 10 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Types of Alternatives—Human Tests - 5 of 10 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Types of Alternatives—Human Tests - 6 of 10 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Types of Alternatives—Human Tests - 7 of 10 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Types of Alternatives—Human Tests - 8 of 10 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Types of Alternatives—Human Tests - 9 of 10 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Types of Alternatives—Human Tests - 10 of 10 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Types of Alternatives—Isolated Organs (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Types of Alternatives—LAL test (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Types of Alternatives—Mathematical Models (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Types of Alternatives—Miscellaneous (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Types of Alternatives—Models (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Types of Alternatives—Monoclonal Atibodies (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Types of Alternatives—Neomorts (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Types of Alternatives—Observation (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Types of Alternatives—Placenta (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Types of Alternatives—Plants (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Types of Alternatives—Plastic Models (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Types of Alternatives—Registries (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Types of Alternatives—Robots (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Types of Alternatives—Visuals (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Types of Experiments—Alcohol - 1 of 5 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Types of Experiments—Alcohol - 2 of 5 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Types of Experiments—Alcohol - 3 of 5 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Types of Experiments—Alcohol - 4 of 5 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Types of Experiments—Alcohol - 5 of 5 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Types of Experiments—Allergy (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Types of Experiments—Alzheimers - 1 of 2 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Types of Experiments—Alzheimers - 2 of 2 (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - Types of Experiments—Arthritis (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - Types of Experiments—Atherosclerosis (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - Types of Experiments—Blood (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - Types of Experiments—Brain - 1 of 6 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Types of Experiments—Brain - 2 of 6 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Types of Experiments—Brain - 3 of 6 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Types of Experiments—Brain - 4 of 6 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Types of Experiments—Brain - 5 of 6 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Types of Experiments—Brain - 6 of 6 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Types of Experiments—Burns (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Types of Experiments—Cancer—Causes - 1 of 5 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Types of Experiments—Cancer—Causes - 2 of 5 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Types of Experiments—Cancer—Causes - 3 of 5 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Types of Experiments—Cancer—Causes - 4 of 5 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Types of Experiments—Cancer—Causes - 5 of 5 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Types of Experiments—Cancer—Prevention (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Types of Experiments—Cancer—Treatments (Cancer, Cure and Cover-Up, by Patrick Rattigan; “Everyone should know that the ‘War on Cancer’ is largely a fraud”—Linus Pauling: Double Nobel Laureate.-1 of 6 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Types of Experiments—Cancer—Treatments (Cancer, Cure and Cover-Up, by Patrick Rattigan; “Everyone should know that the ‘War on Cancer’ is largely a fraud”—Linus Pauling: Double Nobel Laureate.-2 of 6 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Types of Experiments—Cancer—Treatments (Cancer, Cure and Cover-Up, by Patrick Rattigan; “Everyone should know that the ‘War on Cancer’ is largely a fraud”—Linus Pauling: Double Nobel Laureate.-3 of 6 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Types of Experiments—Cancer—Treatments (Cancer, Cure and Cover-Up, by Patrick Rattigan; “Everyone should know that the ‘War on Cancer’ is largely a fraud”—Linus Pauling: Double Nobel Laureate.-4 of 6 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Types of Experiments—Cancer—Treatments (Cancer, Cure and Cover-Up, by Patrick Rattigan; “Everyone should know that the ‘War on Cancer’ is largely a fraud”—Linus Pauling: Double Nobel Laureate.-5 of 6 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Types of Experiments—Cancer—Treatments (Cancer, Cure and Cover-Up, by Patrick Rattigan; “Everyone should know that the ‘War on Cancer’ is largely a fraud”—Linus Pauling: Double Nobel Laureate.-6 of 6 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Types of Experiments—Car Crash (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Types of Experiments—Cloning (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Types of Experiments—Cryonics-1 of 3 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Types of Experiments—Cryonics-2 of 3 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Types of Experiments—Cryonics-3 of 3 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - Unreliability (of Animal Models)—Addiction (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Unreliability (of Animal Models)—Dental (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Unreliability (of Animal Models)—General/Miscellaneous. Question of objectivity in Biomedical Research; burn research with animals; horror stories of the treatment of live animals, especially rats and dogs. Clippings and photocopies from newspapers - 1 of 2 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Unreliability (of Animal Models)—General/Miscellaneous. Question of objectivity in Biomedical Research; burn research with animals; horror stories of the treatment of live animals, especially rats and dogs. Clippings and photocopies from newspapers - 2 of 2 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Unreliability (of Animal Models)—Parkinson’s (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Unreliability (of Animal Models)—Safety Testing - 1 of 2 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Unreliability (of Animal Models)—Safety Testing - 2 of 2 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Unreliability (of Animal Models)—Specific Organs (Box 103, Folder 8)
- Genetic Engineering, 1.5 linear feet
  - Genetic Engineering—Cloning. ONAL; Arizona Republic; Sunday Times; Washington Post; Telegraph; New Scientist; Guardian—Ethical issues for humans and the treatment of animals—more beef, richer milk; animal rights in the age of cloning (Newsday, New York, May 13, 1997); human cloning—the debate (Christian Science Monitor);Dolly, ethics; articles and photocopies - 1 of 8 (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Genetic Engineering—Cloning - 2 of 8 (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Genetic Engineering—Cloning - 3 of 8 (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Genetic Engineering—Cloning - 4 of 8 (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - Genetic Engineering—Cloning - 5 of 8 (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - Genetic Engineering—Cloning - 6 of 8 (Box 103, Folder 14)
  - Genetic Engineering—Cloning - 7 of 8 (Box 103, Folder 15)
  - Genetic Engineering—Cloning - 8 of 8 (Box 103, Folder 16)
  - Genetic Engineering—Drug Production. The DNA experiment; genetic alteration; breeding and cross breeding (monk Gregor Mendel breeds and cross breeds 22 strains of peas. Biotechnology; mice engineering to produce protein to protect against heart attack, cancer, and pigs produce anti-clot protein (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Genetic Engineering—General—1986 and before or no date. “A Science Report,” by Ed Regis, Omni, n.d. Gina Maranto, “Genetic Engineering: Hype, Hubris, and Haste,” Discover, June 1986, pp. 50 ff. The debate, doubts (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Genetic Engineering—General—1987. Conflict between Rifkin and the “biotech farm.” Conflict and ethics. GAO: Biotechnology: Role of Institutional Biosafety Committees, December 1987: GAO/RCED-88-64BR. (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Genetic Engineering—General—1988. Animal patents—mice engineered to be more susceptible to cancer: Veterinarians involved in animal welfare groups are outraged by the government’s decision to patent an animal: Dr. Michael Fox, Vice President/Bioethics and Farm Animals of the Humane Society of the US, says, “This decision reflects an attitude towards creation as mere ownable property. This is a tragic backwards step for this nation to take.” DMV, June 1988, pp. 1 and 14. Article in The Washington Post Magazine, January 17, 1988, “Jeremy Rifkin Is a Little Worried about your Future,” by David Van Biema. (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Genetic Engineering—General—1989. Rifkin blocks ‘gene therapy’ trials on humans in New Scientist,4 February 1989. “Rifkin: the scourge of biotechnologists.” Transgenic mice, smaller mice for more experiments. (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Genetic Engineering—General—1990. The genetic age. (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Genetic Engineering—General—1991. The human gnome project. Andrej Klimowski, “The Frankenstein Factor,” Weekend Guardian, Saturday-Sunday, Marcy 16-17, 1991; mice custom designed for research. (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Genetic Engineering—General—1992 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Genetic Engineering—General—1993 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Genetic Engineering—General—1994 Leap from lab to medicine is difficult. (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Genetic Engineering—General—1995 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Genetic Engineering—General—1996. Man-beast: perilous Mix? London Daily Telegraph, February 18, 1996. “Splicing animal regulations,” The Nation, March 11, 1996, pp. 16 ff. (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Genetic Engineering—General—1997. Slender folder (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - Genetic Engineering—General—2000 (3 pieces) (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - Genetic Engineering—General—2001 (empty) (Box 104, Folder 15)
  - Genetic Engineering—Patents. Technology and Law (Washington Post, August 20, 1987). Patent office and “gene-customized animals.” Churches unite to halt human gene patents. Patents granted for three types of laboratory mice. Animal patents stirs controversy, ethics concerns among DVMs. New York Times, editorial, April 21, 1987 “Yes, Patent Life.” “Mouse patent is issued to Harvart, World’s First for Higher Life Form. NYT, Wed, Apr. 13, 1988. “Mouse patent produces traps: The ownership of a genetically altered life form raises ethical and social issues,” Globe & Mail, Sept. 3, 1994. CAPA (Coalition against the Patenting of Animals from The Humane Society of the United States; 1994?)- 1 of 4 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Genetic Engineering—Patents - 2 of 4 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Genetic Engineering—Patents - 3 of 4 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Genetic Engineering—Patents - 4 of 4 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Genetics (General)—1998 About animal research (slender folder) “Genetic trespassing and environmental ethics,’ Dr. Mira Fong, Center for Global Philosophy, Santa Fe, NM; article about Jeremy Rifkin, president of the Foundation on Economic Trends—to seek a patent to prevent creation of animal-human creature—animals that carry human genes, from the San Francisco Chronicle, April 3, 1988. (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Genetics (General)—1999 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Hair. Alopecia and the assistance of rats in solving the problem of baldness induced by chemotherapy (Wall Street Journal, Friday, September 28, 1990). (Slender file). (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Head Injury. Animals used. Booklet with list of system Projects using non-human mammals to study human impact and trauma. A Few of the federally-funded projects categorized as a waste of tax dollars and animal life (Medical Research Modernization Committee 1985?); head injuries in the chimpanzee. Bashing of cat’s skulls - 1 of 3 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Head Injury - 2 of 3 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Head Injury - 3 of 3 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Hearing/Noise. Testing for jet-noise stress; dolphins and the results of explosions. Annotated bibliography: Anthony P. Majors and Albert C. Myrick, “Effects of Noise on Animals: Implications for Dolphins exposed to Seal Bombs in the Eastern Tropical Pacific Purse-Seine Fishery,” November 1989, 46 pp. (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Heart Disease - 1 of 2 (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Heart Disease - 2 of 2 (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - Heat Stroke/Temperature. Treatment of animals to see how they respond to heat. “Animal agony and heat stroke research” from Animal Welfare Act: Unreported Crimes?” United Action for Animals, Inc. Treatment of baboons in a study by Duane W. Proppe of the Department of Physiology, University of Texas Health Sciene Center at San Antonio.(Leg Blood Flow in Heat-Stressed dehydrated Baboons, 1986,) (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Hepatitis (large file) (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Hepatitis (large file) (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Herpes (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Hodgkins (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Hormones (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Huntington’s Disease (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Immobilization (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Type of Experiment—Gunshot wounds. Dog used as subject. (Box 106, Folder 8)
- Pest Control
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Bats (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Birds—Crows (1 of 2) (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - "Pest Control"—Types of Animals—Birds—Crows (2 of 2) (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Birds—Ducks/Geese (1 of 6) (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Birds—Ducks/Geese (2 of 6) (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Birds—Ducks/Geese (3 of 6) (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Birds—Ducks/Geese (4 of 6) (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Birds—Ducks/Geese (5 of 6) (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Birds—Ducks/Geese (6 of 6) (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Birds—General/Miscellaneous (1 of 4) (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Birds—General/Miscellaneous (2 of 4) (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Birds—General/Miscellaneous (3 of 4) (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Birds—General/Miscellaneous (4 of 4) (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Birds—Pigeons (1 of 6) (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Birds—Pigeons (2 of 6) (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Birds—Pigeons (3 of 6) (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Birds—Pigeons (4 of 6) (Box 107, Folder 17)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Birds—Pigeons (5 of 6) (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Birds—Pigeons (6 of 6) (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Birds—Seagulls (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Birds—Swans (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Cats (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Crustaceans (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Dogs (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Dolphins (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Elephants (Box 155, Folder 9)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Fishes (Box 155, Folder 10)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Frogs (Box 155, Folder 11)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—General/Miscellaneous (Box 155, Folder 12)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Insects—Ants (Box 155, Folder 13)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Insects—Bees (Box 155, Folder 14)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Insects—Cicadas/Locusts (Box 155, Folder 15)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Insects—Cock Roaches (Box 155, Folder 16)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Insects—Crickets (Box 155, Folder 17)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Insects—General/Miscellaneous (1 of 9) (Box 155, Folder 18)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Insects—General/Miscellaneous (2 of 9) (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Insects—General/Miscellaneous (3 of 9) (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Insects—General/Miscellaneous (4 of 9) (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Insects—General/Miscellaneous (5 of 9) (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Insects—General/Miscellaneous (6 of 9) (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Insects—General/Miscellaneous (7 of 9) (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Insects—General/Miscellaneous (8 of 9) (Box 156, Folder 7)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Insects—General/Miscellaneous (9 of 9) (Box 156, Folder 8)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Insects—Gypsy Moth (1 of 3) (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Insects—Gypsy Moth (2 of 3) (Box 156, Folder 10)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Insects—Gypsy Moth (3 of 3) (Box 156, Folder 11)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Insects—Medflies (Box 156, Folder 12)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Insects—Mosquitoes (Box 156, Folder 13)
  - “Pest Control”—Types of Animals—Insects—Slugs (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Burro (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Insects—Kangaroos (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Insects—Koalas (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Insects—Termites (Box 156, Folder 14)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Insects—Ticks (1 of 3) (Box 156, Folder 15)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Insects—Ticks (2 of 3) (Box 156, Folder 16)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Insects—Ticks (3 of 3) (Box 156, Folder 17)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Primates (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Rabbits (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Raccoons (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Raccoons (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Reptiles—General (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Reptiles—Snakes (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Rodent—Beavers (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Rodent—General 2” - 1 of 8 (Box 108, Folder 14)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Rodent—General 2” - 2 of 8 (Box 108, Folder 15)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Rodent—General 2” - 3 of 8 (Box 108, Folder 16)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Rodent—General 2” - 4 of 8 (Box 108, Folder 17)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Rodent—General 2” - 5 of 8 (Box 108, Folder 18)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Rodent—General 2” - 6 of 8 (Box 108, Folder 19)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Rodent—General 2” - 7 of 8 (Box 108, Folder 20)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Rodent—General 2” - 8 of 8 (Box 108, Folder 21)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Rodent—Glue Traps—Correspondence (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Rodent—Glue Traps—Experimentation (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Rodent—Glue Traps—General/Miscellaneous (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Rodent—Glue Traps—Manufacturers (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Rodent—Glue Traps—Retailers (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Rodent—Glue Traps—Statements by Veterinarians (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Rodent—Rats and Mice—Humane—1 of 3 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Rodent—Rats and Mice—Humane—2 of 3 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Rodent—Rats and Mice—Humane—3 of 3 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Rodent—Rats and Mice—Inhumane- 1 of 5 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Rodent—Rats and Mice—Inhumane- 2 of 5 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Rodent—Rats and Mice—Inhumane- 3 of 5 (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Rodent—Rats and Mice—Inhumane- 4 of 5 (Box 109, Folder 13)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Rodent—Rats and Mice—Inhumane- 5 of 5 (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Rodent—Squirrels (Box 109, Folder 15)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Sea Lions (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Skunks (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Ungulates—Bison - 1 of 3 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Ungulates—Bison - 2 of 3 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Ungulates—Bison - 3 of 3 (Box 110, Folder 5)